



01138435866



burgsebastian94@gmail.com



in/burgossebastian



burgossebastian.com

### **SKILLS**

#### Programing

- HTML
- JavaScript
- CSS
- React

### 2D Design

- 3D Max
- Rhinoceros
- Maya
- Zbrush

### 3D Design

- Photoshop
- Autocad
- Ilustrator
- CorelDraw

## Video Editing

- Camtasia StudioAfter Effects
- Adobe Premiere Pro

### Languages

Spanish: Native

English: Advanced

# Sebastian Exequiel Burgos

3D/2D Designer - Programmer

# **About Me**

3D/2D Designer and programmer, passionate about computing and technology in constant search to increase my knowledge in the computer field with great facility to learn new tools.

Professionally I have more than 5 years of experience as an industrial designer.

Complete studies in 3D Design and animation for cinema, including advanced knowledge in various graphic design and multimedia editing programs.

# **Experience**

**Computer technician** 2012-2015 Cpufix s.a.

installation of operating systems and software packages repair and maintenance of hardware cpu and notebooks software and driver conflict resolution

Industrial Designer 2016-2022

3D/ 2D Design and development of machinery and dies

Plc ladder and sequential programming

Cnc Design programming and operation

Design and optimization of 3D Printing

Maintenance of company computer equipment

# **Education**

## **Bachiller Completed**

**Economics and Accounting** 

**Institute Don Bosco 2011** 

Delcapack s.a.

### 3D Modeling & Animation

3D/2D Desing Animation & Modeling Multimedia Editing Render y vfx **Image Campus 2012-2016**